zingiri.com 2013-11-22

# Privacy policy | Zingiri

##  Privacy policy 

### Updated March 2009

#### Table Of Contents

#### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number

#### The Way We Use Information

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### How You Can Access Or CorrectYour Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by [calling us or sending us an email](http://www.zingiri.com/contact-us). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](http://www.zingiri.com/contact-us).
